A DI DE or 9A B OD AN VL 71 ON 9E.
♫‫أ دي دي دي O R 9A B‬♫ ‫OD AN VL 71 ON‬ ‫تسعة‬
BAMORO 9ABOBOANVL7ION9E
BAMOR9ABOANVION9E
I heard from Ah Lu that
سمعت يا لو تقول
she saw Xu Xi's ghost again.
رأت شبح شو شي مرة أخرى
What does that mean?
ماذا تعني
It's scary.
إنها مخيفة
She's crazy and unreasonable.
إنها مجنونة
She's just worried that the world will be in chaos.
‫كل يوم تخاف من عدم الفوضى في العالم
Don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك
I think she's just emotionally unstable.
أعتقد أنها فقط غير مستقرة
She's under a lot of pressure.
الضغط النفسي كبير جدا
You should understand her.
يجب أن تفهمها
I understand her.
أنا أفهمها
Who understands me?
من يفهمني
Actually, I understand.
في الواقع أنا أفهم
what women fear most is being insecure.
أكثر ما تخاف النساء هو عدم الشعور بالأمان
Don't mention Xu Xi in front of her.
لا تذكري شو شي أمامها فيما بعد
I...
أنا
try not to show up in front of her.
‫سأحاول ألا أظهر أمامها‬
It's not Kiki.
‫لا Kiki‬
There's nothing between us.
‫ليس لدينا شيء‬
Why do you care about what others think?
لماذا تهتم بأفكار الآخرين؟
But what if
لكن إذا
I really like you?
أنا أحبك حقا
I...
أنا
I almost forgot the business.
كدت أنسى العمل
Mr. Ji told me something happened, right?
قال لي المدير جي أن هناك مشكلة صغيرة أليس كذلك
To be honest,
بصراحة
the base has been suspended.
تم إيقاف العمل في القاعدة
I’m worried every day.
أنا مشغول كل يوم
The company is a mess
الشركة في الحياة والموت
The house is a mess too.
المنزل فوضوي أيضًا
Yes.
نعم
A man who wants to succeed
رجل يريد النجاح
is afraid of family disagreement.
أكثر ما يخاف هو عدم التعايش العائلي
I'm sorry. I'm not saying you won't succeed.
آسفة، لم أقل أنك لم تنجح
I mean...
أعني
You're right.
أنت على حق
Here's 2 million won.
‫هنا مليون يوان‬
Listen to me first.
استمع لي أولا
Although this is just a little bit of money,
على الرغم من أن هذه الأموال مجرد راتب
at least it can relieve the pain.
لكن على الأقل يمكن تخفيف
President Ji
المدير جي
is trying to help you.
يساعدك
Kaian.
كاآن
Let's put aside our feelings first.
اترك المشاعر أولا
I help you
سأساعدك
because I value your strength
لأنني أحب قوتك
and your potential.
وموهبتك
When everything is over,
عندما ينتهي كل شيء
you'll make a great progress.
سوف تطير إلى السماء
Trust me.
ثقي بي
No, no.
لا لا
I can't take the money.
لا يمكنني أخذ هذا المال
You wish.
أنت تحلم كثيرا
I lent you the money.
‫هذا المال اقترضك
I'll pay you back double when you make money.
‫عندما تكسب المال ستعوضه مرة أخرى‬
Are you a loan shark?
أنت الربا
I'll spare your life.
لن أرحمك أبدًا
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
I'm afraid of you?
أنني أخاف منك
The most important thing is to move.
أهم شيء هو التحرك
Don't stop.
لا تتوقف أبدا
Okay, go ahead.
حسنًا اذهب للعمل
Xie.
لاو شيه
Here is 2 million.
هنا مليون
You know how to use it.
‫هل تعرف كيف تستخدمه‬
I know.
‫نعم‬
Where did you get the 2 million?
‫من أين حصلت على مليون يوان‬
It's none of your business.
لا علاقة لك به
I'm here to tell you
‫جئت فقط لأخبرك‬
stay away from that Kiki.
‫ابتعد عن Kiki‬
Are you done?
‫هل انتهيت أم لا‬
I've thought about it these days.
‫لقد فكرت في هذه الأيام بعناية‬
Every time Kiki appears from the interview,
‫كل ظهور كيكي منذ المقابلة‬
seems to be planned.
‫وكأنها خططت مسبقاً‬
As soon as something haunted happened,
لقد ظهرت شبحًا للتو
she appeared by my side with Xu Xi's voice.
ظهرت بجانبي باستخدام صوت شو شي
Don't you think it's strange?
ألا تعتقد أنها غريبة
Don't be paranoid.
‫لا تكوني مشوشة‬
I know Kiki's voice better than you.
‫أنا أعرف صوت كيكي أكثر منك‬
Of course, you must know her better than me.
بالطبع أنت أكثر دراية مني
But don't forget that Xu Xi learned to dub.
لكن لا تنسي شو شي تعلمت الدبلجة
She's just missing.
لقد اختفت فقط
No one has found out
لم يكتشفها أحد حتى الآن
She came back for revenge.
لقد عادت للانتقام
She wants to destroy us.
تريد تدميرنا
If she wants to destroy me,
إذا أرادت تدميري
she just needs to shut down the company.
‫هي فقط تريد تدمير الشركة‬
as long as the company goes bankrupt.
وتتحمل الكثير من الديون
Why did she help me contact Junteng?
لماذا تساعدني في الاتصال بجون تنغ
Why did she lend me money?
لماذا اقترضت المال لي
Have you really never been cheated?
ألم يخدعك أحد من قبل؟
You wouldn't fall for it if I didn't give you something.
إذا لم أعطيك بعض الحلوى كيف يمكنك خداعها
I know her.
أنا أعرفها
Trust me.
ثقي بي
You must know.
أنت بالتأكيد تعرف
That's what you did back then.
لقد فعلت ذلك في البداية
Liu Kaian.
ليو كاي آن
You're not only a jerk, but also a moron.
أنت لست أحمق فحسب بل أنت ضعيف
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
she will eat you up.
أنها سوف تأكلك
Chen Yalu.
تشين يا لو
Don't affect me with your nerves.
‫لا تؤثر علي بعصابك‬
Kiki is right.
‫كيكي على حق‬
The backyard is unstable.
‫الفناء الخلفي غير مستقر‬
Men are like dogs.
الرجال مثل كلب
I will find out who she is.
سأجد معلوماتها
I want you to kneel down and apologize.
أريدك أن تركع وتعتذر لي
I wish you success.
أتمنى لك النجاح
Get out. I don't want to see you.
اخرج لا أريد رؤيتك
Mother-in-law.
‫زوجة الزوجة زوجة الزوجة‬
Yi Yi is sick.
‫إن يي يي مريضة‬
I just want to take a look. What are you looking at?
‫أريد فقط أن أرى ماذا تنظر‬
What were you doing earlier?
ماذا فعلت في وقت سابق؟
Now you see her as your granddaughter.
الآن تعتبرها حفيدتك
I won't let you see it. Leave.
لن أسمح لكِ برؤيتها، اذهبي
Let me have a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة
I won't let you go.
لن أدعك تذهب
Goodness.
يا إلهي
What's wrong?
ما الخطب يا زوجة القرابة
Let's go.
لنذهب
I don't want to see you.
لا أريد رؤيتك
Mother-in-law.
يا زوجة الزوجة
Let's go.
اذهب بسرعة
I'll leave.
سأذهب
I didn't touch you.
يا زوجة صهري لم ألمسك
Let's go.
اذهب بسرعة
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Your legs are already weak.
ساقك ليست جيدة في الأصل
Why are you fighting with her?
لماذا تتشاجر معها
I'll hurt you again.
إذا جرحتك مرة أخرى
I'm old and useless.
أنا أكبر ولا فائدة
Thank you, miss.
شكراً لك يا آنسة
Come in and have a seat.
تعال إلى الداخل
I'm glad you're fine.
من الجيد أنك بخير
I'll get going then.
سأغادر الآن
Okay.
حسناً
How did she know my leg was sick?
كيف عرفت أن ساقي مريضة؟
Check someone for me.
ساعدني في البحث عن شخص ما
Actor Form.
جدول الممثلة
[Ni Ying Yang as Liu Kaian]
‫ني ليان يانغ تمثل ليو كاي آن‬
Playing Xu Jinxi
‫تشو فو أر تمثيل شو شي‬
Kei as Yan Jiaying
‫يان جيا ينغ تمثل كيكي‬
X Wang as Chen Yalu
‫وانغ شينغ تشن زي تشين يا لو‬
Zheng Tuo jiang as Ji Jiang
تشينج تاوجيانغ
Anyu as Wu Chun Xiang
[وو تشون شيانغ]
Cao Lihua as Xu Mu
تساو لي هوا
Zhang Jianing as Yi Yi.
[تشانغ جيا نينغ]
Liu Weizhou as Lu Wenjun
ليو وي تشو
to perform.
‫المشاركة في العرض‬
Zhu Asia.
‫تشو يا‬
Libin Liu.
ليو لي بين
Zhao, Yu, Wei, Chuan, Zhang Xiaorong.
تشاو يو وي تشوان تشانغ شياو رونغ
Wang, Yi.
‫وانغ يي‬
Jang A-soo.
[تشانغ يا شو]
Lu Cai Yun.
[تشين شين]
Chen Xin.
‫تشين شين‬
XIN Zhao.
‫تشاو شين‬
Han Chao.
هان تشاو
Zhao Yi Cheng.
تشاو يي تشنغ
Wang Tieling.
‫وانغ تيه لينغ‬
Xu Zhenbin.
شو تشن بين
Chen Man-gu.
تشين وان تشيو
Staff Form.
جدول الموظفين
The producer, Huang Haiping.
‫المنتج هوانغ هاي بينغ‬
Director team.
‫فريق المخرج‬
Photography team.
‫مجموعة التصوير‬
Lighting Team.
مجموعة الأضواء
The recording team.
مجموعة التسجيل
Art team.
مجموعة الفن
The styling team.
مجموعة التصميم
Production Team.
‫فريق المنتج‬
[Jo Soo-na]
"جاو سينا".
Hello? Hello.
فريق الشؤون
Driver team.
‫فريق السائق
Tianjin Jiayi Culture Co., Ltd.
‫شركة جيا يي الثقافية في مدينة تيانجين‬
The Disappearing Love.
‫أغنية الحب المفقود‬
Sing, Liu Yaru.
‫أغني ليو يا رو‬
Arrangement: Zhang Xu
‫تصميم الأغاني تشانغ شيوي‬
Production company.
‫شركة الإنتاج
Tientsin Film Pictures Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة للسينما المحدودة في تيانجين
Product Company.
شركة المنتجات
[Tianjin Film Co., Ltd.]
شركة المنتجات المشتركة
Beijing Gaxi Culture Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة للإعلام الثقافية بكين
Beijing Wonderful Forest Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
شركة محدودة الثقافة الغابة الرائعة في بكين
Beijing Deep Technology Co., Ltd.
شركة تقنية عميقة في بكين
Ming Xie Group.
أشكر شركتنا
Tientsin Yu Castle International Hotel.
‫فندق تيانجين يو جيا باو الدولية
Tientsin Hilton Hotel.
"فندق "هاردون" في "تيانجين"
Beijing Handan Steel Hotel.
فندق الميلاد في بكين